reaction to you
реакция тебе
cool cool You have such a set I
круто круто У вас есть такой поставил
understood Yes, just put there is no light
понял Да только поставил света нету
but there will be no light soon there is
но будет скоро света нету унитаз есть
no light there is no light put the washing machine on the
света нет стиральную машинку посадить на
nearest toilet
ближний унитаз
it does not drain probably Come drain the
он не сливает наверное Подойдите слейте
water in it
воду в нем
but for some reason there is no water Why do you need a toilet
а зачем то воды нету А зачем вам унитаз
without water  it’s just worth it for beauty,
без воды он просто стоит для красоты
show more apartments I’m interested,
покажите еще квартиры интересно люблю
but we’ll bring this watering can and we’ll
но этот лейка поднесем
carry it, why is there so little space there
понесем а чего так мало места там
Yes, it’s necessary And what kind of detergent
Да приходится так А какой моющее
melting using only There sometimes
таяние используя только Туда иногда
Sit down Well, yes, then wife, children, this
Присаживайся Ну да тогда жена дети этот
wife, than to buy household chemicals
жена чем вот чтобы в бытовой химии
for cleaning  toilet
покупаете для чистки унитаза
asils probably
асилс наверно
probably so
наверное так
I don’t know this is such a cool
я не в курсе вот это такой крутой
Krasnodar Moscow Vladivostok
Краснодар Москва Владивосток
Elista
Элиста
darists
даристы выбрали
didn’t choose We wanted to show our face but when you
не Мы хотели показать свое лицо но когда
show your face they all
показываешь свое лицо они все
switch I won’t switch I’m still
переключают я не буду переключать я еще
normal to talk Let’s show the
нормально поговорить Давайте показал
toilet immediately stop everything I
унитаз сразу остановись все Я
stopped let’s  while Streltsov I
остановился давайте пока Стрельцов я
switched the face back switch
переключил лицо обратно переключить
I switch
я переключу
this
такой
I was Russian, I was born in Kalmykia
же я русский родился Калмыкии
But my ancestors lived here on these lands and
Но мои предки тут жили на этих землях и
I live Kalmyks Then the Kalmyks arrived
я живу калмыки Потом приехали
Well, somewhere in the 16th century, probably your
Ну еще где-то в 16 веке наверное ваши
ancestors lived there until the 16th century
предки до 16 века там жили за
But these were steppes like Ukrainian The steppe
Но это были степи как украинские Степь
is the Kalmyk steppes
это калмыцкие степи
kharitonovich kharitonovich and  great-great-grandfather Well, the
харитонович харитонович а прапрадеда Ну
one who lived in the 16th century before the
тот который в 16 веке жил до того как
Kalmyks came What was his name
калмыки пришли Как звали
but I don’t remember I remember this
но я не помню я помню бабушку этот
motherly grandmother Akulina Akulina Akulina Matrona
матрёная Акулина Акулина Акулина Матрона
like this
вот так
Well, not 16
Ну не 16
Yes,
Да
it’s then how it
это потом как это
is I can’t know
не могу знать
you can show the
можете холодильник показать
fridge freezer And what’s in the
холодильник морозильник А что там
middle  don’t pull it Wow And what’s there
середине оно не дергайте Ух ты А что там
what’s the coolest Sunrise of the hall there’s everything
что самое крутое Восходе зала есть все
there is one take
есть один это берете
it I don’t know Astrakhan fish Red here
не знаю Астраханская рыба Красная вот
Show Astrakhan red fish
Покажите астраханскую красную рыбу
interesting and have never seen
интересно и никогда не видел
Astrakhan red fish honestly
астраханскую красную рыбу честно
I’m
Я тебе сейчас
ready for you now for example come on how is it
готов например давай ну как она это
cooked  there
приготовлено там
[music] is
[музыка]
visible, but there is
видно но тут осталось
milk left milk
молоко молоко
fat how many norms are there
жиру сколько там норм
sour cream is going to be
сметанка собирается
like that and to the left of the fish what is there a chicken  and
так есть а слева от рыбы что там курочка
baked goose or not
запеченная или нет
Show the goose
гусь Покажите гуся
says the kid called from Kemerovo he
говорит пацан позвонил с Кемерово он с
talks to him friend with Kemero 13 years old
ним разговаривать друг с кемеро 13 лет
kid communicates all over the world
пацану общается по всему миру
half cut off this one for the New Year
половину отрезала этот на Новый год
ate I’m a normal person from Ukraine I
поели я нормальный человек из Украины Я
don’t swear Show me the goose
не ругаюсь Покажите мне гуся
we just have I don’t swear  this is what you
у нас просто Я не ругаюсь это самое ты
think that this is a chicken
думаешь что это курица
such communication
такое общение
for the sake of
ради
a ram
а барана
[music]
[музыка]
pulled it for the New Year of course
дербанил его на Новый год конечно
yes And this is your amplify it from the store
да А это ваш усилить это из магазина
We don’t grow it ourselves but show the belly
Не сами выращиваем а покажите живот
I don’t believe that we grow it ourselves
Я не верю что сами выращивать
with the Wall I will show you these all I will show
со Стеной я тебе покажу эти все покажу
you  as if like savages like
Ты как будто как дикари как
now I won’t show they are sleeping show
сейчас я не покажу они спят покажите
you or something I live in the city I keep a goose
Ты что ли Я в городе живу это гуся держу
I just never I saw
я просто никогда Я видел в мультиках
a goose cow in children’s cartoons There we were taught by
детских там гусь корова Там нас учили
geese Gaga cow mu
гуси Гага корова му
in the store I saw a goose he already I am
в магазине я видел гуся он уже я такое
this  you're chasing me. I'm just going to
этот ты гонишь Просто я сейчас пойду с
talk to you now and you're divorcing me. I
тобой общаюсь и ты меня разводишься я
'm showing you something. I'll go now,
тебе это что-то показываю Я пойду сейчас
you know that
тебе знаешь что еще что-то лучше покажу
I'll show you something
Да гуся не пойду я потому что они спят
better.  I’ll disturb them, but there
не буду их тревожить а кого-то там собак
might be a video inside there, don’t be
внутри может есть ролик не забоишься
afraid of the dark, I’ll show you
темноты я тебе покажу
[music]
[музыка]
yes Well, don’t be afraid,
да Ну давай не бойся
yes,
да
this may be my Internet, this
Вот это может быть у меня Интернет этот
color generator works at the point
цвет генератор работает на точке
Now
Сейчас потихоньку
I’m slowly going out into the street
выхожу на улицу
if this is a camera for you  probably your
если тебе камеры это твой наверное
folk instrument
народный инструмент
I want to show you a folk instrument
твой хочу показать народный инструмент
oh, I
о батюш
don’t see
не вижу
the father But it burned out, it’s true a little
А вот жарился перегорел правда немножко
[music]
[музыка]
Well, yes, I
Ну да
don’t fit because the dog
не подхожу потому что собака
[music]
[музыка]
but show me a big dog,
а покажите мне собака большая еще не дай
God forbid,
Бог
I unfortunately won’t show the goose, my wife will
я гуся к сожалению не покажу жена будет
scold  you write off it comes to you if
ругать ты спишет тебе приходит если
youwere
вы были
immediately visible Henpecked And why is there
сразу видно Подкаблучник А зачем тут
no need for a wife like that You can’t
жена не надо такого Говорить нельзя
say such
такое говорить если
things if I didn’t say anything about my wife right you are
я про жену ничего не сказал правильно вы
afraid I showed you the whole city And you
боитесь Я тебя весь город показала А ты
only yourself So far, show the goose and that’s it
только себя Пока так покажите гуся и все
Well, what’s the problem  goose show
Ну в чем проблема гуся показать
everything they showed it is a problem
все показали они это проблема потому что
because you don’t have this goose you bought it in the
у вас нет этого гуся вы его купили в
store, so if you showed me
магазине значит если бы вы показали вот
two minutes,
две минуты
I’ll give you a second goose  I’ll show you in another
я тебе второго гуся покажу в другом
refrigerator, for example,
холодильнике например
show a dead goose alive I don’t
показывать мертвого гуся живого Я не
believe that people grow geese in cities,
верю что люди в городах выращивают гусей
but there’s a dark one,
но там темного
I’ll show you a
я тебе собаку покажу свет включил собаку
dog  she is sleeping she is controlled
Да нет что она спит она управляется
Why
Зачем тебе
now I’ll show you another that you don’t believe
сейчас другой покажу что ты не веришь
I won’t show the goose Simply
гуся не покажу Просто
But
Но
you see the wife
вот жена видишь 1 2 а там где там еще
wife or from a goose
звук услышишь от жены или от гуся
and a goose she is the sound of a goose Come on say they
а гуся она звук гуся Давай говоришь
are silent she still come on
молчат она еще давай
[music]
[музыка]
with whom you
с кем сидишь
are sitting sleeping I tell you I came here to the
спят я тебе говорю я их вот зашел тут
cinema and they sit
кино и они сидят
for a second I see a goose and turn it off
на секунду увижу гуся и выключай
and I don’t turn on their light because
а я у них свет не включаю потому что
to  they suddenly fight there
чтобы они вдруг они там сражаются
or
или на телефоне
I see a goose on the phone and I will calm down I didn’t
я вижу гуся и успокоюсь Я же не
fall asleep,
заснулись
look we communicated normally I don’t
смотри мы нормально общались я не
swear I’m a normal Ukrainian you’re
матюкаюсь я нормальный украинец ты
normal from Kalmykia Russian Show the
нормальный из Калмыкии русский Покажи
goose what’s the problem
гуся в чем проблема
with  now you are so persistent I’ll show you a
сейчас ты такой настойчивый покажу тебе
goose I’ll turn on the light I’m just my goal was the
гуся свет включу Я просто меня цель была
movie you don’t turn off
кино ты не выключай сейчас
now I don’t laugh that I’m interested in
не я не смеюсь что мне интересно с
talking with adequate people I
адекватными людьми поговорить Я просто
just turned on the light here
сейчас свет тут себя включил
Yes there you have someone laughing too
Да там у тебя кем какой-то тоже смеется
Yes it’s me  someone is laughing on the drum I am
Да это я по барабану кто-то смеется Я я
this myself now I will look at everyone
этот сам сейчас я посмотрю всех
turned on down
включился вниз
there their light is not on just
у меня там свет у них не горит просто
turned off now I Switch the camera
отключилась сейчас я Переключи камеру
No you are smiling as I understand it is
Нет ты улыбаешься так понимаю это
interesting
интересно
three three live geese fly fly live geese
три три живых гуся бляха-муха живые гуси
Awesome
[__]
[music]
[музыка]
we live in Kalmykia today we
живем Калмыкия мы сегодня
eat not imported American anything
едим не привозное американское ничего
there is not European for our products we always eat
там не Европейское на свои продукты едим
other people's products
нам чужие продукты
milk from you from your cow or
молоко у вас от своей коровы или
buy in a store in the sense Well milk
покупаете в магазине в смысле Ну молоко
from a cow or
от коровы или
in 2 why am I telling you
во 2 зачем я тебе говорю
But I will not show it to you here  say
Но я тебе не покажу ее тут скажешь
back Show me
обратно Покажи
there are cows or not
есть коровы или нет
I Subscribe You cheered me up
я Подписывайтесь Ты меня развеселил
usually Russian Ukrainians they quarrel something in chat
обычно русские украинцы они что-то в чат
roulette Why quarrel
рулетке там ссорятся Зачем ссорятся
you can show each other there  there’s already a cow, a
можно друг другу там показать там корову
goose, everyone’s in a good mood True,
гуся уже настроение все хорошие Правда
we are fraternal peoples
Мы братские народы
Well, why fraternal people quarrel and everything
Ну зачем ссориться братски народом и все
I agree with you
я с тобой согласен
[laughter
[смех]
] I can show everything If you came to my
все могу показать Если приехал ко мне
house, they showed all of them in life
домой эти все показал по жизни
in life
по жизни
who is the seller of the store and the
кто продавец магазина да
merchants, I have an excavator worker
коммерсантов походу у меня экскаваторщик
it’s cool
прикольно
at your place or somewhere for work you want to use your
у тебя или где-то на работу хочешь на
excavator
экскаватор
if when I want a hobby now
свой если когда хобби сейчас хочу
Moonshiners try this one
Самогонщики попробовать тут этот
here a little bit if it’s worth it
накапало немножко если стоит
I never sell it for myself I
никогда не продаю я сам для себя делаю
don’t sell anything only to friends I
ничего не продаю только друзьям даю
let you come to visit me I will give you
приедешь ко мне в гости Я тебе дам
moonshine for free  from what you drive
бесплатно самогон из чего гонишь
carry a reward from where
носи награда откуда
I don’t drink,
я не пью
but now I took away the wine from here this
но сейчас я отсюда унес вино этот
360 liters of wine was Let’s
360 литров вина было Давайте
Well, why do I have to drink according to my
Ну зачем мне обязательно пить как по
mood you want to drink you want not
настроению хочешь выпить хочешь не
to drink a year 365 days until if 360 liters of
выпить году 365 дней до если 360 литров
wine a liter a day can be drunk for five days
вина литр в день можно пить и пять дней
there's still a year left for
на трезвость остается еще год
sobriety  you drank something
там настроение Хочешь выпив очень выпил
Maybe you want to ask me something
Может ты меня что-то хочешь спросить Ты
You even showed a goose, maybe you can ask me something,
же даже гуся показал может меня что-то
too, I will answer
спросить тоже отвечу
Yes, I showed you all this, this whole
Да я все это тебе показал этот всю свою
soul As they say, I opened it well, cool I'm
душу Как говорится раскрыл ну классно Я
an open person and that's the thing, come on, I
открытый человек и это самое ну давай я
want to drink  I have 100
хочу выпить вот у меня вот есть 100
grams I just have daughters Birthday
грамм У меня просто дочки День рождения
Tomorrow will be today so I train
Вот завтра будет сегодня так тренируюсь
this
этот
27 years old Tyumen lives
27 лет Тюмени живет
but I won’t show
да не покажу
you my daughter
тебе дочку
Tyumen Tyumen There is such a city
Тюмень Тюмень Есть такой город
far from you And far from me
далеко от вас И от меня далеко от меня
they live
это живут
for a goose Come on,
за гуся Давай
you are a cool guy  Well, at least I communicated with
прикольный ты парень Ну хоть общался с
you, they
тобой
shift and change Yes, but
перекладывают и меняется Да А так типа
they can’t like that. It’s just that I have a talent, I
не могут Просто у меня есть талант я
can see normal good grains in a person,
могу в человеке увидеть
so everyone thinks
нормальные добрые зерно так все думают
some kind of evil man, I understand the
какой-то мужик злой я понимаю
soul, you know,
душу знаешь
that’s why I decided to talk, you showed me a
поэтому и решил поговорить еще ты мне
goose, I’m here  I really saw a
гуся показала я вот реально увидел
live goose I only saw it in the pictures
живого гуся Я только на картинках видел
[music]
[музыка]
Well, you probably wanted to talk more about
Ну ты хотел больше наверно пообщаться по
politics, there is no such thing according to ours, which
политике такой нет по нашей которой
hangs
висит
well
хорошо
there Everything is clear what We were attacked  8 years
там Все понятно чего На нас напали 8 лет
bombed the Donbass, in short, they already went to the
бомбили Донбасс короче пошли уже пошли в
ass, everything is clear But whoever has a
жопу там все понятно А вот то У кого
shorter kigusilka moonshine Damn,
короче кигусилку самогон Блин
I’m shorter, put a pancake on me
я короче я на меня блин
plus
поставьте плюс
put in the chat plus who Just went crazy,
поставьте в чат плюс кто Просто угорал
I’m behaving for a ride So we put a plus sign
веду себя катался Так что нами поставьте
in the chat who is from a goose  I’ve already skated so much
в чат плюсик кто от гуся уже так катался
that my
что короче
stomach and cheekbones hurt shorter and shorter
болит и живот и скулы и всё короче
[laugh]
[смех]
[music]
[музыка]
I’ll put a moment in the recording tomorrow, you’ll
Я завтра в записи потавлю момент
read all the comments
прочитаешь всего комментарии
I’ll pout there to
Я короче дуйся туда
show
показать
[applause]
[аплодисменты]
[laughter]
[смех]